Imagine planning for a peaceful
boat trip to Papikondalu, one
of Andhra Pradesh s most
beautiful spots, only for your
boat to suddenly break down
in the middle of the
water! That s exactly what
happened to 89 tourists recently,
leading to an urgent rescue
operation. This wasn t just
a minor hiccup reports say
the boat developed a snag
while heading towards Papikondalu, turning
a relaxing journey into a
tense wait for help. Luckily,
all 89 people were rescued
safely, but the incident has
big consequences. Boat services from
the Gandiposamma Temple point, usually
buzzing with activity, have been
completely stopped. Think of it
like when your favorite bus
route gets suspended after an
incident, leaving many people looking
for other ways to travel.
Authorities are now looking into
what went wrong and conducting
a fresh safety check for
all other boats. Why is
this a big deal? Papikondalu
is part of the Papikonda
National Park, a huge area
known for its nature and
animals. It s a key
spot for tourism and local
livelihoods. Whenever such an incident
happens, it raises questions about
how safe these trips truly
are. What improvements do you
think are needed to make
sure these scenic boat rides
Subscribe for more breaking news!