Big political drama is unfolding
in Karnataka, and it s
captivating everyone. State Congress President
Shivakumar recently met with top
party leaders Rahul Gandhi and
Mallikarjun Kharge in Delhi. This
meeting happened amid growing speculation
about leadership roles following the
recent election results. Shivakumar s
visit to the capital has
fueled intense discussions regarding who
will be the next Chief
Minister. The Congress party secured
a clear victory, and now
the focus is on how
they will form their government
and decide on key positions.
These high level meetings are
crucial for resolving any internal
differences and presenting a united
front. The outcomes of these
discussions will significantly influence the
state s political landscape in
the coming days. Stay tuned
to ViralDNA for continuous updates
on this developing story and
all the latest news from
your region. Follow ViralDNA to
ensure you don t miss
any critical developments.